YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
时间轴：贝贝求存在感
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： Vero  寒小冰的非小燕  猫中之王  独醉
后期： 渔夫  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY  浪漫已死赛太公    后期：渔夫   字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第八季  第五集
孩子们  你们都知道巴尼叔叔有点狼心狗肺
Kids, it's no secret your Uncle Barney is a bit of a dog,
2030年
虽然他很爱我
and even though he loved me,
但我觉得他一直想找个
I think he always wanted a wingman
跟他一样的狗友做搭档
who was a bit of a dog, too.
在2012年秋天
And in the fall of 2012...
他找到了
...he found one.
致敬
Respect.
伙计们  再次多谢  昨晚太棒了
Hey, guys, thanks again for a great night last night.
我再说一遍
I say again,
昨晚太棒了
great night.
泰德  宝贝  昨晚没那么棒
Ted, honey, it was not a great night.
泰德
Ted,
昨晚我和莉莉注意到有些不对劲
Lily and I noticed some things last night.
-泰德  能帮我递块饼干吗  -好的
- Hey, Ted, can you pass me a cracker? - Yeah.
为了你  我在圣坛上把人甩了
It's the least you can do,
你递个饼干也是应该的
considering I left a guy at the altar for you.
她真搞  对吧
Right, right?
拜托  那是玩笑话
Oh, come on, that was a joke.
过了三十岁的女人  不会拿结婚开玩笑
Women over 30 don't joke when it comes to commitment.
维多利亚很乐意我们放慢脚步
Victoria is happy we're taking things slow.
纯真的小宝贝
Oh, oh, honeysweetiebaby,
没有一个32岁的女人  会乐意放慢脚步
no 32-year-old woman is happy taking things slow.
相信我  维多利亚一定已经有高中同学
Trust me, Victoria has got friends from high school
在Facebook上贴自己第二个宝宝的照片了
posting pictures of second babies on Facebook.
你觉得你女朋友的反应会是
And you think girlfriend's all like,
"咱们就这样耗下去
"Oh, let's just bone a bunch
我又老了一岁  依旧没老公"
so I'm another year older and still single"?
女人呐  你懂不懂
Bitch, please.
各位  我新交了个兄弟
Guys, I've got a new bro--
他能让其他所有的兄弟都自愧不如
a bro that puts all other bros to shame.
他妞见妞爱
The bitches love him.
还会把"大骨棒"藏起来
He buries bones all day.
没人比他更懂追"屁股"跑这事
No one chases tail like him.
你们怎么不笑
Why aren't you guys laughing?
等等  我应该先告诉你们
Oh, wait, I probably should have led with this:
他是条狗
he's a dog.
我已经给他取名叫
I've named him
"把你"
Brover.
我现在要去
I'll go...
"捡"他了
...fetch him.
我很担心巴尼
Okay, I'm worried about Barney.
跟昆茵分手对他的打击  远不止他说的那样
That breakup with Quinn messed him up more than he let on.
我觉得他很寂寞
I think he's lonely.
我看这哥们没事
Dude seems fine to me.
我爱死你了  把你
I love you so much, Brover.
说真的  从昨晚的情形看来
Seriously, based on last night,
你和维多利亚一定会出现问题的
you and Victoria are headed for trouble.
我收到一份有趣的工作邀请
So I got this kind of interesting job offer
是去丹佛经营一间面包店
to run a bakery in Denver.
不过这太疯狂了  对吧
But that's too crazy, though, right?
对吗
Right?
当然
Uh, yeah.
高海拔会影响点心的密度
The high altitude would affect the density of the pastries.
我是说  会烤不熟啊
I mean, talk about half-baked.
天啊  今晚太棒了
Man, this is a great night.
那是维多利亚在邀请你跟她搬去丹佛
That was Victoria asking you to move to Denver with her.
什么
What?
那她为什么不直截了当地
Then, why wouldn't she just come right out
说出她的想法呢
and say what she wants?
男人啊
Men.
这就像是  泡菜罐就得难开
It's like, if there weren't pickle jars to open
蜘蛛就得费心拍死  电脑就跌费神备份
and spiders to kill and computers to back up,
人天生为折腾而存在
what would be their point?
好吧  马修什么时候变得比你还阴阳怪气啊
Okay, when did Marshall become a slightly more feminine you?
泰德  整天主动当人的知心姐姐
Look, Ted, it gets exhausting constantly giving people
太累人了  所以我在训练马修
advice they haven't asked for, so I'm training Marshall.
我的终极目标是
My goal is to eventually say things
能说出犀利又睿智的建议
that are so sassy and wise,
让对方除了认同
that there is no possible response
别无他言
other than "Mm" Or "Mm-hmm."
那我的梦想就是  有天这里能成为
And if this is a place where we can share our dreams--
大家分享美梦的园地
I like to think that it is--
我希望有一天  人们会赞我
I hope someday to earn a...
"言之有理"
"Testify."
维多利亚和我才在一起五个月
Look, victoria and I are five months in
我们现在就该处于这种阶段
and we're right where we should be.
好吧  生日贺卡上签的是各自的名字
All right, we-we're cosigning birthday cards,
我们在彼此家里都有自己的牙刷
w-we got toothbrushes at each other's places,
现在连前戏也省了
foreplay's out the window.
只剩下"我进  我出  睡觉"  简单又快捷
I'm in, I'm out, I'm sleeping, it's great.
你们在一起可不只五个月
It's more than five months.
你们以前约会过  那段时间也算
You guys dated before; that time counts.
可不会分手过就自动归零
The clock doesn't reset to zero.
而是从上次结束的时间接着算
It un-pauses from where you left off.
不可能
No way,
不可能  时钟会归零
no way, the clock resets.
等等  这就是你们的目的吧
Wait, so this is what you guys do?
邀请其他的情侣过来吃晚饭
You invite other couples over for dinner
然后指手划脚以获得优越感吗
to judge them and feel superior?
成熟点吧  泰德
Oh, grow up, Ted,
这是所有夫妻邀请人来家里的原因
that's why any couple invites anyone over ever.
两杯纯苏格兰威士忌
Two Scotches, both neat,
可以来盘坚果[蛋蛋]  他结扎完就没了
and if you've got some, uh, nuts, this guy lost a couple.
开个玩笑  开个玩笑啦
Take the hit, just take the hit.
好吧  他显然是在求助
Okay, this is a cry for help.
今晚能邀请巴尼来吃晚饭吗
Can we invite Barney over for dinner tonight?
但我本来为你准备了特别的晚餐
But I was going to make you a special meal
来庆祝我的节目提名了
to celebrate my show getting nominated
本地区媒体大奖
for a Local Area Media Award.
对了  我忘了说了
Oh, yeah, I forgot to mention,
尼克主持一档有线台的烹饪节目
Nick had a cable access cooking show.
尼克・帕达鲁蒂选用
Chef Nick Podarutti uses
本地新鲜食材
all fresh, locally grown ingredients,
但决不要因此就觉得
but don't think for a second
他不是个坏小子
that means he's not a bad boy.
这车可是玉米动力的哦
She runs on corn.
尼克  坏小子主厨
我要邀请他来共进晚餐
I'm gonna invite him over for dinner.
好吧
Okay, fine,
但你最好确保他有票
but you'd better make sure he has a ticket.
因为他上的可是什锦佳肴火车哦
'Cause it's all aboard the Chow-Chow Train!
亲爱的  我知道想一句
Honey, I know it's hard coming up
个性烹饪口号实属不易
with a signature cooking catchphrase,
可我真心觉得这句不合适
but I don't think that's it.
我知道  可是什么才能跟人家的"嘭"相比啊
I know, but how do you compete with "Bam!"?
美国明星厨师艾梅里尔・拉加西的口头禅就是"Bam!"
言简意赅
It just says it all.
你来啦
Hey, you.
能问你点事吗
Hey, can I ask you something?
莉莉和马修觉得
Um, Lily and Marshall think
我没有领会你的暗示
I'm missing all these hints you're dropping
你希望我们的关系更进一步
that you want a deeper commitment.
你会直截了当告诉我的  对吧
I mean, you'd just come right out and tell me, right?
当然
Totally.
我觉得我能表达得更直接些
I-I think I can be a little bit more direct than that.
谢谢
Thank you.
我今天打扫我公寓的时候
Oh, hey, I was cleaning my apartment today
翻出了这个
and I dug this up.
我该留着这件婚纱吗
Should I keep this wedding dress,
还是你觉得我"永远"都用不着它了
or do you think i'll never, ever need it again?
所以莉莉和马修说对啦
So Lily and Marshall were right?
那是当然
Of course they're right.
一个女孩穿着婚纱跳进你的车里
When a girl jumps in your car in a wedding dress,
难道会很难猜出
you can't act surprised to find out
她是想结婚的吗
she wants to get married.
再说了  我们以前交往过  那段时间也算
Besides, we dated before, and that time counts.
分手只是让时钟暂停而已
We just hit pause on the clock.
很多聪明人会反驳说  分手后时钟会归零
See, a lot of really smart people would argue the clock resets.
是取消暂停  不是归零  这是常识
It un-pauses, everybody knows that.
巴尼有点小迟到
You know, Barney's a little late.
希望他没事
I hope he's okay.
他没事  我还是觉得
Ah, he's fine, and I still don't think
他没在求助
he's crying out for help.
抱歉我们来晚了
Sorry we're late.
我们刚从裁缝那里过来
We just came from the tailor.
把尼选领带时拿不定主意  所以我全给买了
Brover couldn't settle on a tie, so I just bought them all.
谁能对这张萌脸说不
You say no to that face.
你无法全心全意的投入
There's a reason that you're not
与我的感情是有原因的  泰德
a hundred percent in this with me, Ted.
有事让我们停滞不前
Something's holding us back.
是什么
Well, what is it?
我想我们已经确定我不是很会察言观色
I think we've established I'm not great at picking up on clues--
感情方面吧
well, in this situation.
但我小时候可是有名的小侦探
As a kid, I was known as a bit of a detective.
我朋友的牙套保持器不见了
In fact, when my friend's retainer went missing,
莫斯比小子着手调查这件案子  这...
the Mosby Boys were put on the case, and it was...
牙套保持器就在垃圾桶里
The retainer was in the garbage.
莫斯比小子是你  你妹妹
The Mosby Boys were you, your sister,
和小区的一只你自以为驯服了的松鼠
and a neighborhood squirrel you thought you had tamed.
不敢相信松洛克・福尔摩斯会攻击我们
I can't believe Squirrel-lock Holmes turned on us like that.
八周的训练付之一炬
Eight weeks of training down the drain.
你知道我怎么知道的吗  泰德
You know how I know that, Ted?
我们在六年前交往时
Because we covered it in the "getting to know you" part
在"了解对方"的过程中谈到的
of the relationship six years ago.
六年了
Six years.
那是什么让我们停滞不前
Then... what's holding us back?
召回莫斯比小子吧  泰德
Call in the Mosby Boys, Ted,
破案后告诉我
let me know if they crack the case.
伙计们
Guys,
把尼不仅是我交过最棒的兄弟
Brover is not only the best bro I've ever had,
他还对姑娘们很有一套
he's amazing with the ladies.
抱歉  你不觉得用一条狗去勾搭妹子
I'm sorry, don't you think it's a little pathetic
有点可悲吗
to use a dog to pick up chicks?
先生  泡妞搭档是相互帮忙的
Sir, wingmanship is a two-way street.
如果把尼看到靓狗  我会替他挡一刀
If Brover meets a cutie, I'll take the hit
引开胖乎乎的狗闺蜜
and chat up the chubby lady friend.
有时我会充当坏蛋
Sometimes I'll be the jerk...
好让把尼上演英雄救美的把戏
...so Brover can swoop in and be the hero.
如同所有的泡妞搭档一样
And like any good wingman,
我会在前线尽可能地多收集情报
I gather as much intel as I can right up front.
你的狗多大
How old's your dog?
五岁
She's five.
按狗龄来算呢
What's that in dog years?
差不多35岁吧
Like, 35.
那我们走了
We're done here.
你们说对了
Well, you were right.
维多利亚说有事让我们停滞不前
Victoria says something's holding us back,
而我却浑然不知
and I don't have any idea what it is.
有什么高见吗  奥普拉
Any brilliant insights, Oprah?
斯特德曼[奥普拉的老公]
Steadman?
说我盖尔吧[奥普拉的女性好友]
Um, try Gayle.
马修  这次你来吧
Marshall, I want you to take this one.
你准备好了
You're ready.
我不确定
Oh, I don't know.
尽管我听到脑后有股微小的声音
Although I do hear this little voice in the back of my head
试图告诉我些什么
trying to tell me something.
那你是内心的女神
That's your inner goddess.
聆听她的话  传达她的主旨
Listen to her, channel her.
如果维多利亚就像炎热的七月里的
If Victoria quenches your thirst like a tall glass
一杯香甜的茶  让你解渴...
of sweet tea on a hot July day...
马修  为什么她有南方口音
Marshall, why is she Southern?
别让他中断和女神的联系
Don't let him break the connection.
你该让她说出真实想法
...well, you got to make an honest woman out of her.
好了  我走了
Okay, I'm leaving.
但  但
But, but,
如果做不到  甜心
if not, well, then, sugar...
你就该让那只夜莺
...you got to let that nightingale
展翅高飞
spread her wings and soar
飞向自己美好明天
to her own beautiful tomorrow.
此言有理
Testify.
你们烂爆了
You guys are the worst.
我人在哪里
Where am I?
抱歉
Sorry.
我是巴尼
Uh, go for Barney.
明白
I see.
完全理解
Totally understood.
包在我身上
I'll do that.
棒极了
Great.
谢谢你哦
Thank you.
电话是"把你"的主人打来的
That was Brover's owner.
估计是她出远门不在家时
I guess, while she was out of town,
"把你"逃了出来
he ran away from his kennel,
现在她回来了  我得把他还回去
and now that she's back, I have to return him.
巴尼  真遗憾
Oh, Barney, I'm so sorry.
没事没事
Oh, it's all good.
请容许我离开一下
Um, excuse me for one moment.
巴尼
Hey, Barney.
苍天啊  为什么
No, no. No, no!
什么
Wha...
维多利亚
Victoria.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
愿意  当然愿意
Yes, of course.
不过还有一件事
There's just one thing.
什么事  尽管说
Anything. You name it.
你得跟罗宾绝交
You can't be friends with Robin.
除非我和罗宾绝交
You won't marry me
否则你就不会嫁给我吗
if I'm still friends with Robin?
等等  她就是令我俩关系停滞不前的原因吗
Wait. She's the thing that's been holding us back?
你们之间有太多的过去了
There-There's just too much history there.
我们第一次分手就是因为罗宾
I mean, Robin's the reason that we broke up the first time around.
罗宾是我们之间的路障
Robin's our roadblock.
罗宾是个伸手不见五指的大深坑
Robin's the deep, dark pit
我们的关系一掉进去就得死
where our relationship goes to die.
不过她是世界上最好的姑娘  优秀公民
But nicest girl in the world. Salt of the earth.
可她现在已经有尼克了
But she's with Nick now.
虽然  他的厨艺秀挺烂的
I mean, sure, his cooking show is lousy
老是说些奇怪的口号
with awkward catchphrase attempts.
我勒个去呀  谁想要吃呀
Oh, my gosh, who's ready to nosh?
谁想打爆白鲑肚子  来点里面的蛆呀
Who's popping a chub for some grub?
关于那个"打爆白鲑肚子"的发言
I offer my deepest apologies
我对对此不满的观众表示深深的歉意
to anyone who was offended by my "Popping a chub" remark.
我会改进改善
I can and will do better.
保证不犯同样的错了
Won't happen again.
那么现在  谁想要吃我的肉啊
And now who's ready to eat my meat?
不会吧
Oh, come on.
可罗宾和尼克在一起很开心
But Robin's happy with Nick,
我和你在一起也很开心
and I'm happy with you.
你看  我刚才都向你求婚了
Look, I, i just asked you to be my wife.
这不就证明我和罗宾之间没什么了吗
Isn't that proof there's nothing between me and Robin?
也许今天你们之间没有
Well, maybe today there isn't,
可谁能保证明天
but what about tomorrow?
下周  或15年后会不会有呢
Or next week or 15 years from now?
我会一直怀疑你俩
I'll always be wondering.
我从不想当那种会说出
I never wanted to be that girl who says
"选罗宾还是我"的女生
it's Robin or it's me,
但是
but, well...
我必须做出抉择
It's Robin or it's you.
你真是最棒的泡妞搭档
You've been a hell of a wingman.
就算你舔自己私处的时候
And even though I think it's kind of gross
我觉得有点恶心
when you pleasure yourself orally,
但我也是深深被你震惊了
don't ever think that means I'm not impressed.
你觉得巴尼能够自己
Do you think that Barney's gonna be okay
把"把你"还回去吗
bringing Brover back?
他当然可以了
Yeah, he'll be fine.
这不光是你"取悦"自己的能力
It's not just the ability to go to town on yourself,
而是你那兴致勃勃的态度
but you do it with such joie de vivre.
我还是觉得我应该陪他一起去
I really think that I should go with him.
可你必须趁着热
No, but you got to eat these crpes
尝尝这些法式薄饼
as soon as they're flambed.
一定会甜到忧伤的
They're gonna be bon appe-sweet!
-烂  -靠
- No. - Damn.
等我回来我们再吃吧
We'll work on it when I get back.
不  我明白
No, I get it.
虽然我一整晚都在忙这个
You know, I only spent all night working on these,
但显然巴尼更重要
but, hey, Barney's more important.
-尼克  -没事  你走吧
- Nick... - It's fine. Go.
总之  也别搞得像生离死别了
Anyway, let's not make a big deal of it.
我们一起玩了几天
We hung out for a few days,
过了些好日子
had some fun...
不值得一提
No big woof.
我不会忘了你的
没有你  我什么都不是
I don't know who I am without you.
真是太扯了
This is crazy.
维多利亚对于罗宾这事简直在胡搅蛮缠
Victoria is being completely unreasonable about Robin,
我的击掌好姐妹一定会同意我
and my snap sister is gonna back me up.
我再说一次
I say again...
我比较能理解维多利亚的想法
I kind of see Victoria's point.
再说一遍  大软糖夫人
Come again for Ms. Fudge?
泰德和罗宾有太多的过去了
Ted and Robin have so much history.
没错  都是过去  老早的事了
Exactly. History. Ancient history.
泰德  今年早些时候你还对她说过"我爱你"呢
Ted, you said "I love you" to her earlier this year.
我没说这事公平  但我能理解她
I'm not saying this is fair, but I get it.
我完全不能理解
I didn't get that at all.
我怎么感应不到我内心的女神了
How could my inner goddess be so far off?
你总有一天会感应到的  亲爱的
Oh, you'll get there, honey.
奥普拉不是一天建成的
Oprah wasn't built in a day.
怎么了
What?
我早先乱来了
I kind of went rogue.
你如果真的很想怀孕
Look, if you really want to have a baby,
那就别吃避孕药了
just stop taking the pill.
你们在3年前的春假滚过床单
You guys slept together at spring break three years ago.
你们绝对是有感情的
That means something.
喜欢舞台剧音乐
Loves show tunes,
完全是购物狂
total shopaholic,
对做爱不敢兴趣
not always pestering you for sex?
克利福德听起来很值得长相守嘛
Um, Clifford sounds like a keeper.
以上都是同性恋爱做的事
马修  你的这些建议都糟透了
Marshall, all of that advice was terrible.
至少比你说
Not as terrible as you saying
"泰德和罗宾应该绝交"要好一点
that Ted and Robin should stop being friends.
我没说要他们绝交  那也太可怕了
I'm not saying they should. It would be horrible.
但如果泰德真的想要和维多利亚在一起
But if Ted really wants to be with Victoria...
泰德  告诉她你不会和罗宾绝交
Ted, tell her that you're not gonna stop being friends with Robin.
我无法想象没有罗宾的生活
I can't imagine life without Robin.
但她不可能会爱上我
But she'll never be in love with me.
也不会陪我共度余生
She'll never be my wife.
她永远不会是与我相伴到老的那个人
She'll never be the person I grow old with.
维多利亚
Victoria...
维多利亚有可能是
Victoria could be.
你说的和我想的一样吗
Are you saying what I think you're saying?
准备好告别了吗
You ready to say good-bye?
多谢你陪我一起来
Thanks for coming with me.
我当年送走我的狗时
Oh, well, you did the same for me
你也帮我了  还记得吗
back when I had to give away all my dogs. Remember?
我们开车到州北你阿姨的农场
Oh, yeah, we drove to your aunt's farm upstate.
她帅呆了
She was awesome.
我喜欢她这个年老充满智慧
Yeah. I love how she was this wise, old,
淡定的女同志农场主
chilled out, lesbian farmer.
才不是  她不是同性恋
No, no, no. She's not a lesbian.
她的农场也没养女同志
Nor does she farm them.
不  那个和她住在一起的女人
No, that woman she lives with,
只是她的特殊好友莫林
that's just her special friend Maureen.
她们住在一起...
They've lived together for...
真舍不得他
Oh, this is gonna be tough.
"把你"真的是史上最棒的泡妞搭档
Brover really was the best wingman ever.
我的天
Oh, my God.
多谢你把
Thank you so much for bringing
-点点先生送回来  -点点先生
- Mr. Sprinkles back. - Mr. Sprinkles...
真是好听的狗名字
is a great name for a dog.
妈咪好想你哦
Mommy missed you so much.
好想哦
Yes, she did.
是这对好心小夫妻照顾你的吗
Did this nice couple take care of you?
真搞笑
That's a laugh.
大兄弟
Big bro.
我得走了  我得...
I got to split. Yeah, I got to,
我得回到我的农场
I got to head back to the farm...
我和我特殊好友莫林住在那里
where I live with my special friend Maureen.
现在我意识到她是我的同性恋终生伴侣
Whom I now realize is my lesbian life partner.
惊喜
Surprise.
好了  我走了
Okay. All right.
你想进来喝一杯吗
So... would you like a drink?
史上最棒的泡妞搭档
Best wingman ever.
这是什么情况
What's all this?
我以为你在生我的气呢
I thought you were mad at me.
之前是的
I was...
但后来我意识到
but then I realized
我必须接受你有亲密的男性朋友这一事实
I just have to accept that you have close guy friends.
不过我可不想让这成为习惯
I mean, I don't want it becoming a habit
让他们在大半夜的把你从我身边偷走
that they steal you away from me in the middle of the night.
但是
But...
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
泰德要见我
Oh, Ted needs to see me.
有没有搞错啊  女人
Oh, for the love of God, woman.
不是你想的那样  他只是想约炮
Oh, it's not what you think. He just wants to have sex.
开玩笑的
Kidding.
只要用手帮他就行了
Just a little hand stuff.
还是玩笑
Kidding again.
泰德其实更喜欢用胸  我这嘴停不下啊
Ted's more of a boob man. I seriously can't stop.
他有什么事
What does he want?
不知道  但他说是急事
I don't know, but he says it's urgent.
真是对不起
I'm so sorry.
我再被偷走一下下就好
Just one more little steal-away.
只要他把你还给我就行
Just as long as he gives you back.
谢谢
Thanks.
那么
So...
你还好吗
are you okay?
是什么的紧急大事件
What is this big, urgent thing
不可以等到明天再说
that couldn't wait till tomorrow?
有件事我必须得告诉你
There's something I have to tell you.
我想了很多很多
I've thought about this a ton, and, um...
我希望结果不是这样  但是...
I was hoping it wouldn't come to this, but...
我不爱罗宾
I'm not in love with Robin, um,
但她就像我的家人
but she's like family to me, and, uh...
我没法断掉这份情
I can't end that.
所以
So...
你能接受吗
can you accept that?
我真心希望有一天你能得到她的心
I really hope you get her some day.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
昨天晚上
So, last night
泰德叫我去酒吧谈一件紧急事
Ted calls me out to the bar to talk about something urgent.
猜猜是什么
Guess what it was.
他想写一部年轻人的系列侦探小说
He wants to write a series of young adult mystery novels
书名为《莫斯比小子》
called The Mosby Boys.
你为什么要告诉我这个
Why did you need to tell me that?
你是媒体界人士  你有人脉
You work in the media. You know people.
首先  不要写莫斯比家两呆子
Okay, well, first of all, lose the Mosby nerds
聚焦在能破案的松鼠上
and focus on that crime-solving squirrel.
写它绝对书能大卖
That guy is gold.
第二  下次
And secondly, next time
你在深夜有了什么好点子
you have a big idea late at night,
请你去烦你的女朋友
please bug your girlfriend about it.
事实上
Uh, actually...
维多利亚和我分手了
Victoria and I broke up.
我的天
Oh, my God.
为什么  出什么事了
Why, what, what happened?
我们只是理念不同
We just, you know, wanted different things.
太遗憾了  哥们
I'm so sorry, buddy.
但往好的方面看
But, bright side...
罗宾知道你因为她
Robin is gonna be so touched
和维多利亚分手  她会非常感动的
when she hears you ended things with Victoria because of her.
永远不能让她知道
She can never know.
你们要保证永远不会告诉罗宾
Promise me Robin will never find out.
我不明白
I don't understand.
保证
Promise.
-我保证  -我保证
- Promise. - Promise.
当然  罗宾后来知道了
Of course, Robin did find out.
这个以后再说
But we'll get to that.
兄弟  救命
一个疯婆子说我搞大了她的肚子
原来你的蛋蛋还留着啊
So you do have balls.
快跑
Run.